Don't jump!
Think of your family!
Think of your wife!
Who am I?
Where am I?
My life...
How did it come to this?
And...
Not just once.
A second time.
A third time.
Four times.
This one doesn't count.
Five times.
Six times.
Seven times.
Eight times.
I don't get it either.
How did things get so messed up?
Just why?
Is the universe just out to get me?
Why won't this open?
Why can't I get in?
If you could get in,
what would they need us for?
Bro, can you make an exception?
I just need to grab some personal stuff.
I'll be right out.
G-get lost, now.
If you keep messing around here,
believe me, I'll beat the crap out of you.
Wait, I'm the author of this book.
Why won't you let me in?
Hello, Ms. Jin.
Ms. Jin! Ms. Jin!
So many people.
Excuse me.
Just give me half a minute.
My keycard isn't working.
Let me introduce you.
This here is Mike.
While studying abroad in the US,
he majored in health and nutrition.
And a healthy lifestyle is exactly
the current trend in urban living.
So we plan to have Mike
serve as the group's brand ambassador.
Hey, man.
Easy, easy.
So he's our colleague now?
He used to be, but not anymore.
What? What do you mean not a colleague?
Not a colleague? No, no.
We realized that
no matter how we fake your trending stats,
you don't have any real fans.
Your book's content is definitely out of touch with the market.
Young people nowadays
aren't into that cheesy self-help stuff.
That's a flaw in our strategy as well.
But that's completely normal.
It's business.
Business.
Not a single real fan?
Could there be a mistake?
Why don't you take another look?
Also, I just want to go up and get...
Why don't you look for another job?
No, I just want to grab my things.
We're done working together.
She only hired me because of you.
Now that she's giving up on you,
she's dumping me too.
Just like that.
Look, at her level,
all she wants is emotional satisfaction.
You should learn from Mike.
He used to just be
a gym membership salesman.
Can't you just move forward?
With a company as big as ours,
isn't there anywhere I can pitch in?
Can the newbies even make coffee right?
Besides, I'm still a
deputy editor, after all.
Haowen.
About that deputy editor thing... corporate didn't approve it.
Given your current situation,
if you still want to publish your poems,
your best shortcut is still to woo Jin Furong.
What exactly happened between you two?
You offended her,
and you're putting me in a really tough spot.
Success
is about having worked hard,
struggled,
and persevered.
Even if the ending isn't that perfect,
you still have the courage to face the future.
Have you no shame, Fang Haowen?
You're an intellectual.
So what if I'm an intellectual?!
I've lost my love.
I can't just throw away my career too!
I'm at a complete dead end.
What good is saving face?
Tell me, what's the use of it?!
I just want you to have a little dignity.
I don't need it!
At least be true to your own conscience!
I can't!
Not even a little!
Slap me in the face if you've got the guts!
I'll really slap you!
Do it!
Which one of you is scanning the code?
Furong!
Rong'er!
Are you off work yet?
I-I-I... I w-w-wanted...
...to talk to you about something.
Can't drive any further. Just park here.
Baby, come on. Easy, easy, easy.
Park here, park here, park here.
Park wherever you want.
Alright.
You can also park over there.
Or park right here.
Okay.
I'm telling you,
you didn't drink earlier.
When we get back, this whole bottle is yours.
Wait a sec.
I'll close it.
Close it.
Babe! Babe!
Grab me some pajamas, babe.
Okay, baby.
Baby, you have so many pajamas. Which one?
Want me to come out and help you pick?
Never mind. Just pick one for me.
Alright.
I'm thirsty. I want some water.
Thirsty, huh?
Babe, champagne's here.
Baby, you didn't bring me a glass.
Where are the glasses?
On the cart on the left.
Okay, babe.
Coming.
Baby, I'm heading out first.
Make sure you wash up nicely.
Xiaobao, turn off the lights.
Why are the lights off?
Xiaobao, turn on the lights.
Grant me a peach blossom haven, a haven...
Don't leave me heartbroken...
With no one to comfort me...
Babe.
You're taking so long. You meanie.
Come here, babe.
Baby...
Hold on, hold on.
Who's there?
Who is it? What was that noise?
Xiaobao, please turn off the lights.
Who's there?
Who is it?
Stop right there!
You!
Catch him! Catch him!
Xiaobao, turn on the lights!
Fang Haowen!
I wanted to surprise you.
It's called a scare.
I almost called the cops.
You're even wearing a dog collar, huh?
Hand it over.
Look, let me just say...
My phone...
is on the sink in your bathroom.
Go get it for him.
Please, can I just ask...
what exactly did I do wrong?
Can you give me one more chance?
Let me ask you something.
How did you get in?
Last time I brought you home...
you told me the passcode.
Let me tell you something.
You can never come in here again.
Or I'll call the cops on you.
You also told me...
you said you admired my talent.
You have absolutely no talent.
So were you admiring my body?
If you didn't admire my talent,
why would you let me write a book?
I could've gotten anyone to write a book.
If it weren't for me,
would your crappy book have been published?
Furong.
You... you can insult me, but...
don't insult my work.
Bullshit. Your work?
That is my work.
Have you ever been successful?
How many successful people have you interviewed?
And you write "What Is Success"?
Do you really think
you're on the same level as them?
You're a nobody.
Without me,
you couldn't publish a book.
That book is mine.
Th... That's the book I wrote.
How could it be yours?
You wanted to write poetry.
I made you write a textbook.
The textbook belongs to our company.
The copyright is mine.
But the content is mine, isn't it?
I got someone to publish it for you.
Got someone to fake the stats for you.
Hired fake fans for your press conference.
Even the inscription on the cover...
I wrote it for you, didn't I?
I practically held your hand to type!
Write, my ass!
It's been half a year, right?
I hyped that book up so much,
and now look at your conversion rate!
And why is that?
Because your writing sucks!
You're useless!
You have absolutely no talent!
Who do you think you're relying on?
Turns out you're so ugly on the inside.
Just like you are on the outside.
I've been sick of you for a long time.
You know that?
And you wanted me to kiss you.
Truly disgusting.
You...
are a bloated mess.
Get the hell out!
And you, listen to me.
Change the passcode immediately.
Pick any random numbers.
Don't let him in ever again.
If you let him in again,
I'll fire you.
Got it?
Please park shared bikes in designated areas.
Can't you drive?!
Where are your manners?!
Did the rain get into your brain?!
Thinking about finding a partner?
Do you have any criteria?
Yeah, I do.
I don't care how successful
my partner is.
As long as he loves me, and only me,
that's enough for me.
She ran off with that travel agency boss.
We realized that
no matter how we fake your trending stats,
you don't have any real fans.
I knew it! How could that be?
Not a single real fan.
Your book's content is definitely out of touch with the market.
Young people nowadays
aren't into that cheesy self-help stuff.
Since my first book wasn't what I really intended,
I'll write one that fixes my past mistakes.
A book free from constraints.
A truly free book.
A book that mocks hustle culture.
Wang Fuxiang.
Bye, Haozi.
I'm leaving this filthy place.
To chase after freedom.
Hope your new book is a hit.
Here, take it. Fifty.
Please... give me a bit more.
I'm only doing this because you intellectuals have it rough.
If anyone else tried to sell me waterlogged books,
I would've smacked them right across the face.
The new book is done. Publication is just around the corner.
Jiahuan.
Let me run something by you.
What is it?
I finished my second book.
Finished it, huh?
Congrats. Congratulations.
That's really great.
Listen, could you...
pull some strings for me?
And just get it published?
And I'll still hire you as my agent.
It's 2026 already.
Don't you have better things to do after work?
Who's gonna buy this book of yours?
Just trust me.
Take a look. It's really good.
Really good.
It's full of raw emotion.
I just sent it to you.
Fang...
Nobody's going to publish a book for you now.
If you want to publish this,
you'll have to pay for it yourself.
That's gonna cost two or three hundred thousand.
Do you have that kind of money?
How about you spot me the money first?
Hello?
Hao.
It's Fang.
Got a quick update.
I've already finished my second book.
It's a poetry collection. It's really good.
Do you think... think you could...
use... use your connections to pull some strings?
And find a publisher for me?
Fang,
it's not that I don't want to help.
Our company's business hasn't been great lately.
We only survived because Furong
bought us out.
My hands are tied here too.
Why don't you try asking Furong?
Let's drop that.
It's been a while since we caught up.
Let me tell you,
I've recently gotten really into golf.
Wanna come with me sometime?
Bro... bro, to tell you the truth,
I'm... right now, I'm...
What's wrong?
in a bit of a tight spot.
I see.
Um, about the book last time,
Didn't Jin Furong pay 200,000? See,
could you give me a cut?
Hello, is Mr. Li in?
No, he's not.
Hello, miss.
Is Mr. Ruan in the office?
Is Mr. Qin here?
Mr. Li.
Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Wu.
Zhou.
Liu.
Mr. Zheng.
Mr. Zhang.
Sun.
I couldn't reach you at all, so I came to your house.
Get lost!
Okay.
Xiyou.
Excuse me.
Can I take two minutes of your time?
I need to tell you something.
I just wrote a book.
It's at a crucial stage right now.
And at a time like this,
I might need...
My condolences. My condolences.
I'm so sorry. So sorry.
I'm leaving the media company.
I joined this company...
I came here to achieve
my childhood dream.
And what did I actually achieve?
I achieved a pile of crap here.
That day you threw me under the bus for Hao,
claiming those nipple covers were mine!
I felt awful.
I just didn't want you to miss out
on a single
chance to get into Hao's inner circle.
Why didn't you do it then?
That's not what I want to talk to you about today.
I want to tell you...
Don't we write articles?
Don't we do journalism?
What we should be documenting
is ordinary people's
reality.
Just... just these people. These...
these people's real living conditions.
But what happened?
What the hell did we write?
We just wrote about rich people's
hypocritical lives.
There's absolutely zero truth to it.
Don't you like writing?
You can write anywhere.
Just not here.
I want to go somewhere with beautiful scenery.
With no people.
No skyscrapers.
No concrete jungles.
And no crap.
Where did the crap go?
I mean, I'm leaving.
Haozi,
you're a guy with dreams.
You should come with me.
This place is too filthy.
We need to go somewhere clean and sanitary.
My place is probably cleaner than your pockets.
Which one of you is paying the bill?
I got it, I got it, I got it.
That night, I stayed with him the whole time,
unable to utter a single word.
Fuxiang.
Haowen.
How have you been?
Me?
I... I...
I've been busy writing lately.
It wore me out completely.
I just remembered to reply to your message.
Alright?
Right, your...
that thing you wrote...
"Wearing Truth, Embracing Hypocrisy."
I saw it, it's pretty good.
"Piercing Hypocrisy, Embracing Truth."
Right.
You read it?
I saw the ad.
I haven't had time to read the book yet.
Please don't buy it.
I must give you a copy in person.
Haowen. Alright, alright.
Let me show you.
Take a look.
The beautiful view.
I'm telling you,
the place I'm at right now
has absolutely gorgeous scenery.
I'm telling you, you have to come over.
That night,
just like the night before he left,
I was speechless.
Alright, it's a deal.
Honey.
Come here, come here.
Wang Fuxiang talked endlessly about his experiences and romance.
I felt like a bystander.
Haowen...
Mrs. Wang, Mrs. Wang.
And then that afternoon,
she suddenly gave me a kiss.
Then I said,
I have to kiss her back.
Then she kissed me again. Are we drinking without any snacks?
At least order a couple of skewers.
What do you want to eat?
I... I'll treat you to a few skewers.
Haowen.
I'm gonna get back to work.
Bye, Mrs. Wang.
Mrs. Wang is so nice.
That night, Wang Fuxiang kept thanking me.
He said that without me,
he wouldn't be where he is today.
Without you,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
I need to toast you.
Haozi,
hurry up and come over!
I'll be waiting for you right here.
Alright?
How... how did things go with you and Wang Yue?
Good evening, sir.
I'll be your flight...
The great writer Fang.
Traveling by yourself?
How have you guys been?
Pretty good.
You're here for Wang Yue, right?
Wang Yue quit six months ago.
Where did she go?
You didn't know?
Wang Yue is getting married.
To that...
That guy from your celebration party.
Liu Zhao'en.
They're so in love.
She just married a rich guy anyway.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
You actually came.
Give this to her for me.
Pretty thick.
Must be twenty thousand in here.
Gold?
Chocolate.
It's twenty thousand calories.
Who does that?
Two bottles of Moutai on every table.
Must've cost a fortune.
Tell me about it.
Dear guests, family and friends,
Life is a vast ocean, an endless journey.
Through its ups and downs,
Miss Wang Yue
is now stepping into the rest of her life.
The most touching thing about love
is the certainty of choosing each other.
The bride, carrying the fruit of their love,
approaches with gentle yet firm steps.
The hope in the bride's heart,
the passion in the groom's eyes,
will, with every step she takes,
become a timeless moment.
Let us wait with great anticipation
to welcome this
grand entrance of love and commitment.
On one knee
I do
Ignore him.
No whispering allowed.
I'll come back in a bit
to give you a private toast.
Come on, don't go.
Yueyue.
Haozi.
Let me introduce you.
Fang Haowen, a famous writer.
Get to know each other later.
I am a successful and famous writer.
My second book
has already been published.
There are many people I want to thank,
but the one I want to thank most is my fellow townsman...
Wait, no.
My old classmate.
Go eat. Go on.
Yue.
We haven't seen each other for so long.
And you just get married out of nowhere.
And you get pregnant just like that.
So what?
Do I need your permission to get married and pregnant?
Are you my dad?
Just kidding, right?
I'm just kidding.
What's up, Haozi? Are you drunk?
Why did you marry him?
He's a really great guy.
He's honest, and doesn't have much education.
He runs a small travel agency and always gets taken advantage of.
When a guy is this nice,
his business won't grow big.
But he treats me incredibly well.
And he's very innocent.
Innocent?
Innocent? I know exactly what happened.
He swooped in when you were vulnerable!
Are you drunk?
Sit down, just sit down.
Is it any of your business?
Well, take your time eating and drinking, everyone.
Don't I know if I'm drunk or not?
How is it not my business?
I know exactly if I'm drunk!
It has absolutely nothing to do with you!
Let's have another drink.
Come on, don't just stand there.
Mark my words, all of you.
Hello?
Ladies and gentlemen,
today is the big day for Ms. Wang Yue and Mr. Liu...
Mr. Liu Whatever-en.
These two people,
the one they should thank the most is me, yours truly,
a man of letters, modern poet, Fang Haowen.
Also known as the Solitary Bard.
How do I feel right now?
It's like mistaking aged vinegar for ink,
writing a half-lifetime of sourness on the page!
Let me give you all a grand introduction,
Fang Haowen,
author of "What is Success?",
the matchmaker for Wang Yue and me.
That's right. Right here.
I'm their matchmaker.
I'm their witness.
Earlier, Wang Yue was praising you,
praising this... Whatever-en.
Saying how innocent he is.
Whatever-en, do you think you're innocent?
Are you innocent?
I don't think you are.
How did these two meet?
Let me tell you all.
The very first time they met
was at my celebration party.
Very interesting, right?
After some drinks,
he took her home.
What's my point in saying all this?
You have to treat her...
Hey!
Who muted my mic?
Come turn it back on!
Turn it on! Hurry!
You have to treat her well.
You... you have to treat Wang Yue well.
Do you understand?
Know what I mean?
It hasn't been easy for Wang Yue.
She came to Huanxi City all by herself.
She had absolutely nothing.
Between you and me, she chose you.
What is this?
An honor for you.
You must cherish it!
You...
Come down, come down!
Have you had too much to drink?
Why make a scene at Wang Yue's wedding?
I came back too late.
If I had come back a bit earlier,
would Liu Zhaoen even have a chance?
Wang Yue and I would have long ago...
What do you know?
Going up there to run your mouth!
Were you even there?
Did you see it or what?
I did see it!
Liu Zhaoen took Wang Yue inside the house,
and he
came right back to drink with us.
After that,
Liu Zhaoen spent an entire month,
chasing Wang Yue for a month,
and they haven't even held hands.
You don't know shit!
I don't believe it. Do you?
Wang Yue is so gorgeous,
and Liu Zhaoen is a normal guy.
He took her into the room,
just the two of them, laid her on the couch,
even covered her with his clothes,
closed the door on his way out,
and even turned off the lights.
You guys are so innocent.
Do you work at a bookstore?
Some intellectual you are.
You have the dirtiest mind.
You left with that sugar mama first that day, didn't you?
Fine.
Looking sharp.
Thinking about finding a partner?
Do you have any criteria?
I want a stable home
and someone who loves me.
I don't care how successful
my partner is.
As long as he loves me, and only me,
that's enough for me.
After I drop Furong off,
I'll head right back.
Head right back. No rush.
Drink up, drink up!
Right.
S-sorry, sorry, I'm sorry!
Wang Yue, you don't know.
I wrote a poem for you.
I was going to give it to you when we got married.
I
was revitalized
by the act of loving you.
Therefore,
when you
serve as the ending to "I love you,"
"I"
becomes a verb.
"Love"
reverts to being a noun.
My love
is just like
eating,
breathing,
surviving.
You turned me into
a continuous life activity.
Love
is essential to sustain life.
Everything started with you.
You caused the three words "I love you,"
once a perfectly complete sentence,
to be forcibly separated by commas.
That's why
saying every single word
has become so difficult.
Hey guys in the chat,
this is a dangerous stunt.
Don't try this at home!
Don't jump!
Think of your family, think of your wife!
Young man, are you done with that bottle?
Come down and sell it to me!
Oh no, I couldn't talk him down!
I hate this world.
I hate myself.
Young man! Young man!
Please don't jump!
Come down, Auntie will take you square dancing!
Don't jump! Don't jump!
You don't have to pay the rent in a week!
You can pay it later!
My mom made me rush you!
What are you saying?!
If I could start over...
Coming.
I'm coming.
Why are you mad?
Your... your friend
I don't know them.
If I could start over
I can sell
three million in one night!
You're definitely worth a fortune for one night.
That's just an estimate.
It could actually be more.
Selling books on a livestream.
Selling out completely.
I'll flash my underwear on the livestream!
I'm on a livestream! Flashing my underwear!